<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AntiLitter</string>
    <string name="s1">Fact: The average person generates over 4 pounds of trash every day and about 1.5 tons of solid waste per year.</string>
    <string name="s2">Fact: It is predicted by the year 2050 that there will be more pounds of plastic in the ocean than fish.</string>
    <string name="s3">Fact: The most littered item is fast food packaging. The chance of people littering these kinds of items increases greatly on highways.</string>
    <string name="s4">Fact: One million birds and 100 thousand sea animals are killed every year as a result of being trapped in or eating some litter item.</string>
    <string name="s5">Fact: Littering is illegal. Fines vary by state and by city and county, you will be charged if you are caught littering.</string>
    <string name="s6">Fact: Litter is very expensive. Every year millions of taxpayer’s dollars are spent cleaning up litter.</string>
    <string name="s7">Fact: Litter spoils water quality. The hazardous waste seeps into soil and can cause groundwater pollution.</string>
    <string name="s8">Fact: Litter can lead to animal attacks as animals are drawn closer to civilization.</string>
    <string name="s9">Fact: About 25,000 car accidents in the US are caused by litter each year.</string>
    <string name="s11">Fact: One littered plastic bottle can take 450 years to decompose.</string>
    <string name="s12">Fact: South Carolina contributes the most litter and Washington state contributes the least.</string>
    <string name="s14">Fact: Motorists account for 53% of all litter produced annually.</string>
    <string name="s16">Fact: Litter contributes to the 15 to 51 trillion particles of floating micro plastics in our oceans, weighing between 205\-520 million pounds.</string>
    <string name="s17">Fact: Approximately every square mile of ocean has more than 45,000 pieces of plastic floating in it.</string>
    <string name="s18">Fact: Fish often can’t tell the difference between littered plastic and food. If the animal eats plastic, they can’t digest it.</string>
    <string name="s19">Fact: Approximately one truckload of plastic enters the ocean every single minute.</string>
    <string name="s20">Fact: Littered styrofoam takes 80 years, littered aluminum takes 200 years, and littered plastic takes 400 years to decompose.</string>
</resources>
